{
    "subject": "resource/Privilege_Ibiza",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Privilege Ibiza is the \"world's largest nightclub\" according to the Guinness Book of Records, with a capacity of 10,000 people. It is located not far from San Rafael, Ibiza, less than 1 km from the nightclub Amnesia. For fourteen years, Privilege hosted Manumission, one of the island's most famous events. After a dispute between the club owner and Manumission's organizers, the event moved to Amnesia.Originally called Ku, Privilege was a restaurant in the 1970s.",
    "human_readable": "According to the Guinness Book of Records, Privilege Ibiza, which is 'world's largest nightclub', has a capacity of 10,000 people and is located near San Rafael, Ibiza.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9442455172538757,
            "question": "What is the name of the world's largest nightclub according to Guinness Book of Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9184684157371521,
            "question": "Is Privilege Ibiza a popular nightclub?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8765249252319336,
            "question": "Which record does Privilege Ibiza hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8603528738021851,
            "question": "Where is Privilege Ibiza located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8571681380271912,
            "question": "Near which city is Privilege Ibiza situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7706769108772278,
            "question": "What kind of events might be held at Privilege Ibiza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7160341739654541,
            "question": "How many people can Privilege Ibiza accommodate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6995819807052612,
            "question": "Who might visit Privilege Ibiza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5456869602203369,
            "question": "Can you describe the atmosphere at Privilege Ibiza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5392139554023743,
            "question": "What island is Privilege Ibiza on?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=According to the Guinness Book of Records, Privilege Ibiza, which is 'world's largest nightclub', has a capacity of 10,000 people and is located near San Rafael, Ibiza.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2894_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the atmosphere at Privilege Ibiza?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2894_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might visit Privilege Ibiza?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2894_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many people can Privilege Ibiza accommodate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2894_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2894_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2894_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2894_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2894_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2894_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2894_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2894_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2894_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2894_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2894_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the triple:\n\n* The first document contains the phrase \"According to the Guinness Book of Records\" which suggests that Privilege Ibiza's information can be found in this source.\n* The following documents (24, 29, 48) confirm that Privilege Ibiza is indeed the world's largest nightclub according to the Guinness Book of Records.\n* Document 6 also states that \"The 'Privilege' is the best choice for everyone\u2019s desires and can be found on the Balearic Islands\" which supports the location of Privilege Ibiza being near San Rafael, Ibiza."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the provided context documents support the statement. The documents confirm Privilege Ibiza's status as the world's largest nightclub according to the Guinness Book of Records, its capacity for 10,000 people, and its location near San Rafael on the island of Ibiza."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}